

CONTACT

szijpeter@gmail.com

+36205651265

github.com/szijpeter

Budapest

EDUCATION

COMPUTER SCIENCE ENGINEER BSC

2006-2009

Budapest University of Technology and Economics

LANGUAGES

Hungarian native English profficient German beginner

PETER SZIJ

Mobile developer

ABOUT

Android developer by heart with 10 years of experience in building, optimizing, testing, publishing and maintaining various mobile apps. I am fluent in Java but nowadays I really like to write my code in Kotlin. I like to solve problems and keep a tidy garden. I can work best in small agile teams or individually.

TECHNOLOGY STACK

Java
Kotlin ♥
ConstraintLayout ♥
Gradle
Git
CI/CD (with GitLab)

RESTful APIs
GraphQL
Firebase and Play Services
Swift (little rusty)
React-Native (recently)
TypeScript

EXPERIENCE

BIG FISH INTERNET-TECHNOLOGY LTD, BUDAPEST

Senior mobile software developer | 2014-Present developing various mobile applications and libraries mostly on the Android platform

MTA SZTAKI DEPARTMENT OF DISTRIBUTED SYSTEMS, BUDAPEST

Mobile software developer | 2010-2014 developing mobile applications on Android and iOS

INFOMATIX KFT, BUDAPEST

Software developer | 2009-2010 developing the company's framework for Android platform

SHOWCASE









